[
  {
    "Question": "Fill in the correct word. അവൾ നിനക്ക് പണം വല്ലതും തന്നോ? Did she give you __ money?",
    "Answer": "any"
  },
  {
    "Question": " Fill in the correct word. ഷെൽഫ് വൃത്തിയാക്കുന്നതിനിടയിൽ ഞാൻ ഗ്ലാസ് പൊട്ടിച്ചു. I broke the glass while __ (clean) the shelf",
    "Answer": "cleaning"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Fill in the correct form of the word -good. She is _____ than me.",
    "Answer": "better"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How many pots ____ every week? (അവൾ ആഴ്ചയിൽ എത്ര പാത്രങ്ങൾ ഉണ്ടാക്കാറുണ്ട് ?)",
    "Answer": "does she make"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How do you say this in English?  നിങ്ങൾ എപ്പോഴെങ്കിലും സിംഗപ്പൂരിൽ പോയിട്ടുണ്ടോ?",
    "Answer": "Have you ever been to Singapore?"
  },
  {
    "Question": "അവൾ എങ്ങനെ പോയി? How to say this in English?",
    "Answer": "How did she go?"
  },
  {
    "Question": " Fill in the correct form of -break. Have you ___ your glasses?",
    "Answer":"broken"
  },
  {
    "Question": "അവൻ എല്ലാ ദിവസവും ഓട്സ് കഴിക്കാറുണ്ട്. How dp you say this in English?",
    "Answer":"He eats oats every day"},
  {
    "Question": "Fill in the correct word. She has taken care of her ___ 2010",
    "Answer":"since"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Fill in the appropriate form of the word -bad. This is a bad book. That book is ____ (ആ പുസ്തകം അതിലും മോശമാണ്)",
    "Answer":"worse"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Fill in the correct word(s). What ___ she eat? അവൾ എന്താ തിന്നാറു? ",
    "Answer": "does"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Fill in the correct form of verb go. She has ____ to the mark",
    "Answer":"gone"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Fill in the correct word. He is ___ best doctor in this hospital",
    "Answer":"the"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Fill in the correct word. എനിക്ക് എന്റെ സഹോദരിയേക്കാൾ പ്രായമുണ്ട്. I am ____ than my sister",
    "Answer":"older"
  }
]

